FUNMILAYO MAKANJUOLA

Am a product of positivity

Experience: 3 years | Available: Immediately | Location: Ibadan & Oyo State

makanjuolaff@gmail.com | +2348035381429

ABOUT ME



Expert level proficiency with MS Office Suite (MS Word and Excel Spreadsheets)

Topnotch communication, analytical and organizational skills, with the ability to multitask and prioritize Proven ability to lead top-performing teams, in line with a company's strategic objectives

WORK EXPERIENCE



nysc scheme

Graduate trainee | Administrative assistant Ikare , Nigeria 2011-08-01 | 2012-08-01

Managed and disbursed funds, maintained financial records and prepared reports; ensured sufficient funds are available to meet ongoing o operational and capital investment requirements.

Negro consultant Nigeria Limited

Entry level | Administrative officer Ilorin , Nigeria 2014-07-01 | 2015-10-01

Oversaw administrative processes: basic bookkeeping, inventory control, correspondence handling, document preparation and database management. Main duties include managing inventory, preparing regular reports (e.g. expenses and office budgets) and organizing company records.

Jemi-alade travels and tour

Entry level | Public relation officer Lagos , Nigeria 2015-12-01 | 2016-12-01

Enhanced the company's public image; developed and implemented PR strategies and campaigns; prepared press releases, keynote speeches and promotional material; built and maintained positive relationships with

stakeholders, media and the public.

Oris support services

Mid level | Credit officer Ibadan , Nigeria 2020-01-01 | 2020-10-01

- *Handling and disbursement of cash to customers.
- *Sourcing for new clients and maintaining The old ones.
- *Handle The organization phone calls,ledger,account and disbursement book.
- *Working under pressure to meet organization set goals.

Gifted one farms

Senior level | Farm administrative manager Ibadan , Nigeria 2020-12-01 | 2021-07-01

- ✓ in charge of coordinating an organization's administration system and general workflows.
- ✓ Guiding the organization's activities
- ✓ Identifying opportunities to improve
- ✓ a business' policies or objectives
- Ensuring a company is operating securely and effectively
- ✓ Preparing and reviewing operational reports
- ✓ Leading and/or participating in meetings

EDUCATION

Ä

Kwara state polytechnic

| Business administration

Business administration certificate at Kwara state polytechnic

Kara state polytechnic

HND | Marketing

Administrative support.

Office management Customer relationship managemen

LANGUAGE SKILLS

I

English

Yoruba

CERTIFICATES & AWARDS

Certificate in data processing: Certificate | 2012